In this video we will talk
about ICICI Lombard
and the market cap of the company is
67 thousand 825 crores and the secret of the stock is also that the
company gives a dividend of 0.258
and now if we talk about the positive points in the company then the
company has reduced its debt and the
company is almost debt free and the
profit tax of the last 15 years is
2375 and the debit of the company is 21 point
and now if we talk about the negative points in the company then at present the
stock is trading at 768 from its book value
and in the last two-three
years the holding of the promoters has reduced by 7 point
50%
and now if we talk about the profit of the company then
862 crores
1049 crores
1194 crores
1473 crores
1304 crores have been
seen in the profit of the company this year
and if we talk about the shares then cover it by 30 and
now let's look at the year 2009 but
in the body of the motor  The
holding of 4805 promoter has decreased to
51 point 8948 point zero five
and the holding of income 28 point 12, we have also
reduced our holding 28 point
4128, but
in this quarter
Rafi has increased his holding and in
Degree Harding Hatyara 47 Designer has
increased his holding from point 52 to
Tera Pocket 47 and in the public's
holding Terapanth 36 public holding has
also increased from 18 to 10 to 36
but in this quarter compared to the previous quarter, the
public holding has decreased
and here you can see that Yes
Securities has
given a target of fifteen hundred twenty rupees
and now if we talk about the chart of the company, this
percentage rise has been seen in the city today, at present the
share price
is 1383 rupees and the support in the share is 13 ₹100 and at
this time RSS of 641
in Amazon  And this hair was sold for ₹1600.
At present it is available at a discount. You
can buy it for ₹13,100. That's all in this video. If you liked the
information seen in the video, then
like the video, share it and
subscribe to our channel.